First Last

Node.js Developer

Creative Node.js Developer with 6+ years of strong experience in Operating Systems & Terminal, Machine Learning areas while managing the interchange of data between the server and the users.

San Francisco, CA 12345 +1 234 567-890 first.last@resumeworded.com linkedin.com/in/resumeworded

EXPERIENCE

Growthsi, New York, NY

Regular Node.js Developer

January 2020 - Present

- Gathered and validated requirements as a part of a collaboration for a progressive web application that helped develop clear, unambiguous technical requirements and establish a consistent feedback loop.
- Coordinated with 3 other teams to identify customer requirements, creating 16+ BRD and tech documents that streamlined development activities.
- Performed full-stack development of the high-profile external web app, resulting in 5 bug-free releases deployed promptly and within standards.
- Maintained newly developed and existing systems for a mission-critical external web app utilizing Azure Functions, NHibernate, and Jenkins.
- Optimized legacy data storage and search query for the high-volume external web application, minimizing the average response time by 63%.

Growthsi, New York, NY

Node.js Developer

July 2016 - December 2019

- Assisted in developing server-based Node.js software by providing inputs and insights, acquiring a 15% increase in the quality of overall work.
- Provided strong technical leadership and guidance to 5 TD project and development teams, including teams that are geographically distributed that resulted in consistent and effective daily operations and processes.
- Delivered HTML 5 application developed by other internal groups, gaining necessary expertise and skills in collaboration and communication.

Resume Worded, Boston, MA

Node.js Developer Intern

January 2015 - June 2016

- Created 2 custom general use modules and components extending the elements and modules of core AngularJS, obtaining outstanding results.
- Wrote a non-blocking code using numerous advanced techniques and strategies such as multi-threading & JavaScript dependency management.
- Wrote 3 front-end use cases using tech stack to meet business needs.
- Tested 2 Angular JS applications via Jasmine and protractor, acquiring an excellent overall performance rate of 92% for the specific task.

SKILLS

CSS

HTML Javascript Mocha should.js Supertest API HTML 5

Core AngularJS

Jasmine

Protractor

Azure

NHibernate

Jenkins

MongoDB

EDUCATION

Resume Worded IT University

BS Computer Science November 2014

Boston, MA

CERTIFICATIONS

Resume Worded IT University

Node.js Certificate May 2016

Boston, MA